A Finding Aid to the National Society of Mural Painters Records, 1895 - circa 2007, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
National Society of Mural Painters records
1895 - circa 2007
Archives of American Art
National Society of Mural Painters (New York, N.Y.)
AAA.natimurp
Archival Resource Key
13.1 Linear feet
The records of the National Society of Mural Painters measure 13.1 linear feet and date from 1895 to circa 2007. The activities of the society are documented through administrative files, membership files, correspondence, committee files, exhibition and competition files, artist files, financial and legal records, printed material, a scrapbook, and photographic materials.
Conditions Governing Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment. Use of archival audiovisual recordings with no duplicate access copy requires advance notice.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The National Society of Mural Painters lent materials for microfilming in 1963 and donated records in 1965-1966. The National Society of Mural Painters, via President Jeff Greene, gave papers in 2009.
Separated Materials
The Archives of American Art also holds material lent for microfilming (reel NSM1) including 83 photographs of mural paintings and mural studies, and 25 exhibition boards showing sculptures, mosaics, and mural paintings with the artist's name, medium, title, and location listed. Lent materials were returned to the lender and are not described in the collection container inventory.
Scope and Contents
The records of the National Society of Mural Painters measure 13.1 linear feet and date from 1895 to circa 2007. The activities of the society are documented through administrative files, membership files, correspondence, committee files, exhibition and competition files, artist files, financial and legal records, printed material, a scrapbook, and photographic materials.
Administrative files include meeting minutes and agendas, historical information, and newsletter drafts, and the organization's constitution and by-laws. Membership files contain correspondence with members about their applications and acceptance or denial of membership, member voting ballots, and lists of members. General correspondence is with artists, members, organizations, universities, and federal commissions, and documents a wide varity of NSMP activities; additional correspondence is scattered throughout other series. Correspondence is with Charles Baskerville, Arthur Covey, Allyn Cox, Dean Fausett, Ruth Fortel, Edward Lanning, Everett Molinari, Jack Stewart, and Helen Tredwell, as well as with the American Federation of Arts, the Commission of Fine Arts on War Memorials, Fine Arts Federation, and the U. S. Capitol Historical Society.
Committee files document the work of various NSMP standing and ad hoc committees. Exhibition and competition files include correspondence, photographs, catalogs, itineraries, and printed materials for the NSMP's 1976 U.S. Bicentennial celebration projects, including the "Freedom Murals," "Caravan of Freedom," and "Momentous Events in American History." Additional files document the Red Cross Canteen Project, Federal Art Project, the Municipal Art Society exhibition in 1940, New York City subway murals, and other competitions and public art mural projects.
Artist files primarily date from the 1960s through the 1990s and often include biographies, resumes, correspondence, and photographs of works of art. Financial and legal records include the NSMP treasurer's files, ledgers, and miscellany. Also found in the records are printed materials; a mixed media scrapbook dating from 1923-1935; photographs of meetings, events, exhibitions, and works of art; photo collages of members with examples of their works of art. There are also lantern slides of Francis D. Millet in his studio and with his murals, and of J. Scott Williams with his art work.
Biographical / Historical
Originally named The Mural Painters, the National Society of Mural Painters (NSMP) was founded in 1895 in New York City by a group of artists, including John W. Alexander, Kenyon Cox, Edwin Blashfield, and John LaFarge, who were concerned with the design and execution of mural art for architecture in the United States. The organization's first president was Frederic Crowninshield. For well over one hundred years members of NSMP have created significant and monumental works of art across the country. Many significant American artists have been members and served as past presidents, such as George Biddle, Hildreth Meiére, Arthur S. Covey, Allyn Cox, Helen Treadwell, and Xavier Gonzales, among many others.
Since its founding, the NSMP has collaborated with the Fine Arts Section of the Treasury Department, the federal WPA Arts Project, and the design boards of several World's Fairs. As a member of Artists for Victory, NSMP coordinated the execution of murals for barracks and camps, as well as many triptych alterpieces.
NSMP organizes exhibitions and conductes competitions. In celebration of its one hundredth anniversary, a centennial exhibition was held in October 1995 at the Art Students League. Society members work with other organizations, actively sponsoring legislation for the development and commission of public works of art. Still active today, the current president is Jeff Greene.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 10 series reflecting the original order of the records.
Missing Title
Series 1: Administrative Files, 1895-circa 2007 (2.2 linear feet; Boxes 1-3)
Series 2: Membership Files, 1915-2001 (1.1 linear feet; Boxes 3-4)
Series 3: Correspondence, 1912-2001 (1.0 linear feet; Boxes 4-5)
Series 4: Committee Files, 1909-1960s (0.3 linear feet; Box 5)
Series 5: Exhibition and Competition Files, 1917-1998 (2.0 linear feet; Boxes 5-7)
Series 6: Artist Files, 1915-1990s (1.3 linear feet; Boxes 7-8, 18)
Series 7: Financial and Legal Records, 1895-1996 (1.5 linear feet; Boxes 8-10)
Series 8: Printed Material, 1915-2000 (0.9 linear feet; Boxes 10-11)
Series 9: Scrapbook, 1923-1935 (0.2 linear feet; Box 11)
Series 10: Photographic Material, circa 1900-1997 (2.5 linear feet; Boxes 12-18)
Existence and Location of Copies
Portions of the collection and material lent for microfilming are available on 35mm microfilm reels D248-D250A and NSM1 at the Archives of American Art offices and through interlibrary loan. Researchers should note that the arrangement of material described in the container inventory does not reflect the arrangement of the collection on microfilm.
Other Finding Aids
Microfilm reels D248-D250A: Microfilm inventory available at Archives of American Art offices.
Lantern slides; Photographs; Muralists -- United States; Subways -- New York (N.Y.); Scrapbooks; American Revolution Bicentennial, 1776-1976; Artists' studios -- Photographs; Art -- Study and teaching; Mural painting and decoration -- 19th century -- United States; Mural painting and decoration -- 20th century -- United States; Cox, Allyn, 1896-1982; Fortel, Ruth; Millet, Francis Davis, 1846-1912; Molinari, Everett; Lanning, Edward P.; Treadwell, Helen, 1902-; Williams, J. Scott (John Scott), b. 1877; American Federation of Arts; Red Cross; Municipal Art Society of New York; Fine Arts Federation of New York; Federal Art Project; Baskerville, Charles, 1896-; Covey, Arthur Sinclair, 1877-1960; Stewart, Jack, 1926-2005; United States Capitol Historical Society; Fausett, Dean, 1913-
- Administrative Files, 1895-circa 2007; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 2.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-3
  Scope and Contents
  Administrative files contain material regarding the society's activities, founding, and history and include meeting minutes and agendas, drafts of newsletters, constitution and by-laws, and other miscellaneous documents and one videocassette. Files labeled miscellaneous likely contain duplicates of other material documented throughout the collection.
  - Annual Dinner and Meeting, 1910-1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Chapters, Regional, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1915-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4-7)
  - Guest Register, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Historical Information, circa 1950-circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Historical Information, NSMP #1, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letterhead Design, 1940, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mailing Lists, circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1895-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13-23)
  - Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1940-circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1-19)
  - Miscellaneous Administrative Files, Likely Duplicates, 1919-circa 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20-23)
  - Miscellaneous Administrative Files, Likely Duplicates, 1919-circa 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, Drafts, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Website Design and Permissions, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Membership Files, 1915-2001; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 1.1 Linear feet Boxes 3-4
  Found is correspondence relating to the application, acceptance, and decline of membership from 1916 to 1954 and the 1990s. Also found are lists of contact information for members and voting history and ballots. Correspondence about membership applications and acceptance decisions are found for many artists, including George Biddle, Edward Bruce, Kenyon Cox, Allyn Cox, Philip Evergood, William Gropper, Stefan Hirsch, Tom LaFarge, Geoffrey Norman, Violet Oakley, and Ernest Peixotto, among many others.
  - Applications, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Contact Information and Lists, 1915-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5-18)
  - Contact Information and Lists, Honorary, Lifetime, and Professional Members, 1935-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19-21)
  - Correspondence, 1916-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22-32)
  - Correspondence, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Deceased Members, 1919-circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3-5)
  - Membership Cards, 1990s-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
  - Personnel Index, 1917; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Voting Ballots, 1941, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
- Correspondence, 1912-2001; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Boxes 4-5
  Correspondence documents a wide variety of general activities of the NSMP and is with artists, members, organizations, universities, and federal commissions' additional correspondence is scattered throughout other series. Correspondence is with Charles Baskerville, Arthur Covey, Allyn Cox, Dean Fausett, Ruth Fortel, Edward Lanning, Everett Molinari, Jack Stewart, and Helen Tredwell, as well as with the American Federation of Arts, the Commijssion of Fine Arts on War Memorials, Fine Arts Federation, and the U. S. Capitol Historical Society.
  Arrangement
  Correspondence is arranged in rough alphabetical order. Folders with individual names were transcribed from the original folders may include letters to and from that correspondent.
  - A, 1918-circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Art, 1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Andors, Rhoda, 1989-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Artists League of America, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - B, circa 1912-circa 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Baehr, Francine, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Baskerville, Charles, 1957-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - C, circa 1912-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Case, Elizabeth, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Columbia University, 1918-1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Commission of Fine Arts on War Memorials, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Covey, Arthur, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Cox, Allyn, 1960-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - D, circa 1912-circa 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - E, circa 1912-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - F, circa 1912-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Fausett, Dean, 1960s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27-29)
  - Fine Arts Federation, 1917-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30-31)
  - Fortel, Ruth, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Franklin Mint, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - G, circa 1912-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Gonzalez, Xavier, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - H, circa 1912-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Harding, Robert Jr., 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Irwin, Howard Lee, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
  - J, 1977-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Juta, Jan, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - K, circa 1912-circa 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - L, circa 1912-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Lanning, Edward, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - M, circa 1912-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Mahoney, James Owen, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Molinari, Everett, 1980-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Mortellito, Domenico, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - N, circa 1912-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - NanTandy, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Norman, Geoffrey, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Orme, Lydia Gardner, 1941-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - P, circa 1912-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Ross, Louis, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - S, circa 1912-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Selection of Fine Arts, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Slobodkin, Louis, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Stewart, Jack, 1997-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 58-60)
  - T, circa 1912-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Tobey, Alton, 1977-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Treadwell, Helen, 1960s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - U, circa 1912-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Capitol Historical Society, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - V, circa 1912-circa 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Victory Hall Association, 1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - W, circa 1912-circa 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Williams, J. Scott, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Y, circa 1912-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Z, circa 1912-circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
  - Dinner for Ernest Peixotto, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Form Letters, 1940-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Requests for Brochures, 1917-1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Requests for Protest, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - List of Letters Received, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Committee Files, 1909-1960s; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 0.3 Linear feet Box 5
  Committee files contain scattered correspondence, reports, lists, printed material, and memoranda documenting the work of standing and special committees.
  - Amend By-Laws and Constitution, 1921-1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19-20)
  - Beautify New York City, 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Sites, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Coordination, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Current Work, 1917-1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dinners, 1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Education, 1917-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26-28)
  - Executive Committee, 1917-1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Fine Arts Federation, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Government and Art, 1940-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31-33)
  - Large Canvases, 1920-1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Legislation, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35-36)
  - Medals and Awards, 1919-1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Membership, 1917-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38-39)
  - Mural Painting, 1909; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Nominating Committee, 1917; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Professional Practice, 1917-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42-43)
  - Proposed Art Building, 1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Publicity, 1921-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Washington Relations, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46-48)
  - List of Standing Committees, 1919-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Exhibition and Competition Files, 1917-1998; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 2 Linear feet Boxes 5-7
  This series is arranged in chronological order according to the earliest document found for a project. Folders containing material relating to the Bicentennial competitions likely include documents relating to all three projects.
  The bulk of this series consists of material relating to the three NSMP projects celebrating the 1976 U.S. Bicentennial, including the "Freedom Murals", "The Caravan of Freedom", and "Momentous Events in American History". Files include correspondence, printed material, plans, itineraries, scattered financial documents, applications, and some photographs documenting planning, execution of work by members, fundraising, and publicity. Included is an audio cassette recording entitled "Momentous Events at Nabisco." A file for the Mural Night Forum includes a letter and typed remarks given by Elizabeth McCausland. There is a videocassette recording of a dedication of a mural by David Garrison in Fort Madison, Iowa.
  - Red Cross Canteen Project, 1917-1919; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - George W. Breech Memorial Exhibition, 1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Portland, Oregon Exhibition, 1921-1925; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Architectural League, 1921-1922; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Church Competition, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Bronx High School of Science, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Department Store Competition, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Federal Art Project, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Municipal Art Society Exhibition, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Mural Night Forum, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Public Works of Art Competition, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Selection of Fine Arts, Recommendations, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Subway Murals, New York City, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - World's Fair Competition, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 63-65)
  - Whitney Museum Exhibition - Correspondence, 1940 March-August; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Whitney Museum Exhibition - Correspondence, 1940 September-October; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Whitney Museum Exhibition - Correspondence and General Information, 1940 October-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Whitney Museum Exhibition - Entry Slips, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Whitney Museum Exhibition - Lecture, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Ernest Peixotto Memorial, 1942-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Architectural League Exhibition, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Museum Exhibition, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - New York State Thruway Authority Competition, 1973-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Bicentennial Competitions, 1973-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9-36)
  - Bicentennial Competitions, 1976-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-17)
  - Bicentennial Competitions, Momentous Events at Nabisco, circa 1980; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 100th Anniversary Exhibition, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Dedication of Mural by David Garrison, Fort Madison, Iowa, 1997; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Mexico International Exhibition, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Art Students League Exhibition, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22-23)
- Artist Files, 1915-1990s; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 7-8, 18
  Artist files may include resumes, correspondence, photographs of works of art. The bulk of the material dates from the 1960s to the 1990s. Earlier material consists of general artist biographies. Files are found for Robert P. Archer, Tom Capuccio, Peggy Delport, Dean Fausett, Michael Glickman, Robert J. Harding, Frank Mason, James Penny, and Elias River, among others.
  - General Artist Biographies, 1915-1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - General Slide Lists, circa 1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - A, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - B, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
  - C, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - C, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - D, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - E, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - F, 1956-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - G, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - H, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - J, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - K, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - L, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - M, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - N, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - O, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - P, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - R, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - S, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - T, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - V, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - W, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20-21)
  - Y, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Z, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Oversized Photos of Works of Art, circa 1960-circa 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Financial and Legal Records, 1895-1996; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 1.5 Linear feet Boxes 8-10